Guide to the Ray Stevens Ashbery papers, [1930-1971?].
Ashbery, Ray Stevens papers, [1930-1971?].
- Series II. Subject files, 1948-1962. Assembly files, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - To Trumansburg, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Series III. Topic files
  - A. Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment
    - Committee Meeting on Unemployment - Buffalo, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Motion to Discharge Unemployment, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Radio Broadcasts, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Unemployment Insurance - Departmental Bills, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Aug. 20 and 21 - State Advisory Council Meeting - Top O'the World Lodge, Lake George, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - FEPC, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Unemployment Insurance - Correspondence after Session, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Report - Unemployment Insurance, 1961, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Retraining Unemployed Workers, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Vouchers 1952, 1951-1958 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Unemployment Insurance Telephone 5900 - Trumansburg, 1959-1960, 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Unemployment Insurance - Miscellaneous Correspondence, and filing, 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Payroll File #2 - Unemployment Insurance, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Budget Debate, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Unemployment Insurance Finances, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Unemployment Insurance - Ashbery, 1960, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1959-1962 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Report Back Home, 1951-1955 (Box 33, Folder 8-17)
    - Report Back Home - Ã’Barbara TalksÃ", 1955 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Report Back Home, 1956-1961 (Box 33, Folder 19-25)
  - NOTE: Section missing from original listings.
  - Route 13 meeting - Aug. 10, 1950,1958-1959 (Box 33)
  - Route 13, 1950-1951, 1957 (Box 33)
  - Route 13 - 4064 Rules Com...passed A. 3-28-57, 1957 (Box 33)
  - Route 13, 1956-1957 (Box 33)
  - Route 13 relocation - Highways - Tompkins Co., Newfield, 1955 (Box 33)
  - Tompkins Co. - Highway, 1957 (Box 33)
  - 2189. Ashbery - Rte. 13, 1950-1951 (Box 33)
  - Route 13, 1959 (Box 33)
  - Route 13 - 2189 - Ashbery, 1952 (Box 33)
  - Route 13 - 2190 - Ashbery, 1951 (Box 33)
  - Route 13, 1957-1958 (Box 33)
  - Route 13 - Ashbery - A. 2491, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Desk School 1952-53 Miscellaneous, 1949-1953 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - School Desk 1953, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - 54 School 3 Revenue Anticipation Notes, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - 54 School 5 School Election - Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - 54 School 6 Serial Bus Bonds, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - 54 Miscellaneous 27 Tes #1 - Increase of Board Members, 1952-1954 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - 1954 - Desk TC 5, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - 54 School 2 School Guard (Jackonsville and Trumansburg), 1954 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - 55 School 1 1955-56 Revenue Anticipation Notes, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - 55 School 2 Notice of Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - 55 Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - 55 School 5 Annual Meeting, 1951-1952, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - 55 School 7 Mills Family, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - 56 School 1 1955-56 Revenue Anticipation Notes, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - 56 School 2 Notices of Meetings, 1954-1956 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - 56 School 3 School Buses, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - 56 School 4 - Serial Bus Bonds, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - 57 School 1 1956-58 Revenue Anticipation Notes, 1956-1958 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - 57 School 2 Buses, 1954, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - 57 School 5 Prattsburg Telephone Co., Inc. (Assessment), 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - 57 School 6 first Presbyterian Church - lease for outside rooms, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - 58 School 4 School Buses Purchase, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - 58 School 5 Civil Service Employee, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - 58 School 6 1958-1959 Revenue Anticipation Notes, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - 58 School 7 - leases for outside rooms - First Presbyterian and First Baptist Churches, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - 58 School 8 Lehigh valley Railroad - Town of Covert, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - 58 School 10 B & L Motors Driver Training Car, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - 58 School 11 New Building and Bond Issue - defeated, Dec. 18, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - 59 School 1 New Building and Bond Issue - defeated Feb. 19, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - 59 School 2 Rodney Brown, Infant; Gordon Brown, Father - Accident, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - 59 School 3 - Special Meeting - Buses and Bus Notes June 29, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - 59 School 4 - Annual Meeting July 14, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - 59 School 5 - 1959-60 Revenue Anticipation Notes, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - 59 School 6 New Building and Bond Issue, 1953-1954, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - School - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - 1960 School 1 Bond Issue - New High School, 1953-1960 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - 60 School 2 Special Meeting - Buses, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - 60 School 3 Trumansburg Central School Telephone Tax Hearing May 19, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - 60 School 5 Bond Anticipation Notes, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - 60 School 6 Annual School Meeting - July 12, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - 60 School 7 Bond Issue Contracts and Insurance Policies, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Trumansburg School - Bond Issue Oct., 1960 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - School Bonds, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - School - Dedication Sept. 24, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - School - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - School - Special Meeting - Buses and Office Building, 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - 61 School 2 - $1, 200, 000 Bond Issue, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - 61 School 5 Special Meting - School Buses, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - 61 School 4 Revenue Anticipation Notes 150,000 1960-61, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - School - Bus Accident Mar. 1 - (Ed Miller, driver), 1962 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - 62 School Special Meeting - School Buses and Notes Mar. 19 and Aug. 8, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - TCS School Board Meeting Apr. 11, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - School - Bus and Miscellaneous - Repair, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - School - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - School - Annual Meeting, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 69)
- Series IV. Legislative files, 1949-1962 (introduction numbers).
  - 30, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 155 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - 225 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 243 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - 245 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - 406 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - 520 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - 627 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - 683 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - 722 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - 772 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - 772, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - 978 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - 1007 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - 1046 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - 1098 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - 1174 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - 1409 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - 1472 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - 1677 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - 1694 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - 1760 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - 1897 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - 1922 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - 2028 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - 2117 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - 2128 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - 2189 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - 2351 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - 2480 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - 2562 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - 2654 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - 2654 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - 2764 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - 2818 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - 2990 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - 3059 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - 3059 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - 3063 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - 22, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - 43 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - 52 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - 59 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - 110 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - 114 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - 116 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - 120 (S.I. #30) (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - 227 (S.I. #338) (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - 259 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - 306 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - 338 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - 440 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - 466 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - 480 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - 593 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - 634 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - 769 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - 900 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - 901 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - 948 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - 1026 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - 1208 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - 1223 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - 1235 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - 1243 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - 1278 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - 1349 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - 1414 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - 1423 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - 1538 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - 1613 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - 1621 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - 1632 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - 1634 (Box 37, Folder 74)
  - 1638 (Box 37, Folder 75)
  - 1666 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  - 1735 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - 1756 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  - 1955 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - 2039 (Box 37, Folder 80)
  - 2070 (Box 37, Folder 81)
  - 2181 (Box 37, Folder 82)
  - 2197 (Box 37, Folder 83)
  - 2338, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 84)
  - 2403 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 2493 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - 2495 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 2570 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - 2588 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - 2836 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - 2845 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - 2938 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - 2952 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - 2966 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - 3080 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - 3119 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - 3120 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - 3146 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - 3190 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - 3214 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - 3249 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - 3256 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - 3284 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - 1, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - 17 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - 129 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - 130 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - 189, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - 345 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - 354 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - 359 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - 428 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - 658 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - 668 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - 705 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - 714 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - 783 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - 993 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - 1010 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - 1035 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - 1077 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - 1115 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - 1137 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - 1157 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - 1167 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - 1193 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - 1226 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - 1307 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - 1307 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - 1329 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - 1333 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - 1335 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - 1336 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - 1385 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - 1454 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - 1470 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - 1508 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - 1522 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - 1583 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - 1597 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - 160 4 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - 1607 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - 1628 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - 1674 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - 1706 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - 1707 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - 1878 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - 1887 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - 1924 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - 1947 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - 1959 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - 1984 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - 2031 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - 2036 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - 2059 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - 2157 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - 2402 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - 2434 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - 2436 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - 2508 (Box 38, Folder 76)
  - 2617 (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - 2707 (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - 2748 (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - 2852 (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - 2866 (Box 38, Folder 81)
  - 3009 (Box 38, Folder 82)
  - 3030 (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - 3034 (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - 3130 (Box 38, Folder 85)
  - 3155 (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - 3177 (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - 3223 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 3277 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 3287 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 2, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 4 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 6 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 23 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 58 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 65 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - 70 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - 84 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - 200 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - 265 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - 269 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - 339 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - 526 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - 532 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - 543 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - 578 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - 602 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - 604 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - 605 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - 630 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - 790 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - 863 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - 990 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - 1031 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - 1096 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - 1339 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - 1162 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - 1214 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - 1234 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - 1731 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - 1754 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - 11847 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - 1848 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - 2048 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - 2405 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - 2497 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - 2541 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - 2671 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - 2780 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - 2781 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - 2824 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - 2844 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - 2887 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - 2967 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - 2968 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - 2969 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - 2970 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - 3024 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - 3046 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - 3090 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - 3091 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - 3092 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - 3101 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - 3125 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - 3126 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - 3306 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - 2, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - 5 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - 10 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - 91 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - 1139 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - 162 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - 169 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - 430 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - 448 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - 460 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - 535 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - 566 (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - 594 (Box 39, Folder 72)
  - 740 (Box 39, Folder 73)
  - 745 (Box 39, Folder 74)
  - 748 (Box 39, Folder 75)
  - 748 (Box 39, Folder 76)
  - 806 (Box 39, Folder 77)
  - 922 (Act. # 2206, 1001) (Box 39, Folder 78)
  - 972 (Box 39, Folder 79)
  - 1018 (Box 39, Folder 80)
  - 1069 (Box 39, Folder 81)
  - 1201 (Box 39, Folder 82)
  - 1242 (Box 39, Folder 83)
  - 1255 (Box 39, Folder 84)
  - 1257 (Box 39, Folder 85)
  - 1504 (Box 39, Folder 86)
  - 1516 (Box 39, Folder 87)
  - 1520 (Box 39, Folder 88)
  - 1554 (Box 39, Folder 89)
  - 1555 (Act #3250, 3251, 3253) (Box 39, Folder 90)
  - 1556 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1646 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - 1691 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - 1750 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 1751 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 1752 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - 1782 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - 1807 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - 1820 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - 1884 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - 1942 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - 2012 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - 2051 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - 2085 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - 2128 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - 2176 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - 2288 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - 2306 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - 2307 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - 2308 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - 2309 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - 2392 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - 2419 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - 2492 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - 2525 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - 2530 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - 2569 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - 2890 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - 2962 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - 2971 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - 2972 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - 3026 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - 3039 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - 3098 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - 3145 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - 3217 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - 4 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - 14, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - 105 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - 200 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - 250 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - 251 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - 452 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - 473 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - 556 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - 653 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - 742 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - 761 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - 906 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - 922 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - 973 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - 1017 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - 1261 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - 1264 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - 1390 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - 1435 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - 1647 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - 1648 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - 1649 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - 1650 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - 1651 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - 1765 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - 1770 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - 1779 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - 1795 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - 1859 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - 1904 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - 2014 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - 2072 (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - 2080 (Box 40, Folder 70-71)
  - 2081 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - 2085 (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - 2171 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - 2360 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - 2526 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - 2592 (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - 2629 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - 2684 (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - 2685 (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - 2686 (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - 2722 (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - 2787 (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - 2843 (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - 2870 (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - 3121 (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - 3129 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - 3192 (Box 40, Folder 88)
  - 3197 (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - 3252 (Box 40, Folder 90)
  - 9, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 91)
  - 10 (Box 40, Folder 92)
  - 13 (Box 40, Folder 93)
  - 23 (Box 40, Folder 94)
  - 99 (Box 40, Folder 95)
  - 130 (Box 40, Folder 96)
  - 134 (Box 40, Folder 97)
  - 164 (Box 40, Folder 98)
  - 173 (Box 40, Folder 99)
  - 177 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 188 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 189 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 228 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - 241 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 252 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - 256 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - 324 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - 353 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - 428 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - 472 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - 474 (Act #2031, 773, 617, 1986) (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - 533 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - 612 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - 674 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - 725 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - 754 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - 759 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - 836 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - 857 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - 875 (Act #1313) (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - 876 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - 918 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - 989 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - 1005 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - 1019 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - 1025 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - 1027 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - 1061 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - 1066 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - 1067 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - 1084 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - 1085 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - 1128 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - 1148 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - 1167 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - 1205 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - 1211 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - 1381 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - 1398 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - 1399 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - 1404 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - 1459 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - 1484 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - 1526 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - 1597 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - 1599 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - 1609 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - 1625 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - 1642 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - 1660 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - 1677 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - 1678 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - 1680 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - 1683 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - 1685 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - 1722 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - 1741 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - 1779 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - 1805 (Act #2309) (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - 1811 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - 1815 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - 1859 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - 1861 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - 1900 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - 1912 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - 1939 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - 1969 (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - 1971 (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - 2016 (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - 2021 (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - 2034 (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - 2048 (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - 2097 (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - 2115 (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - 2120 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - 2123 (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - 2194 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - 2179 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - 2220 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - 2350 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - 2369 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - 2411 (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - 2440 (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - 2460 (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - 2471 (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - 2499 (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - 2522 (Box 41, Folder 88)
  - 2523 (Box 41, Folder 89)
  - 2535 (Box 41, Folder 90)
  - 2564 (Box 41, Folder 91)
  - 2603 (Box 41, Folder 92)
  - 2659 (Box 41, Folder 93)
  - 2674 (Box 41, Folder 94)
  - 2756 (Box 41, Folder 95)
  - 2842 (Box 41, Folder 96)
  - 2843 (Box 41, Folder 97)
  - 2852 (Box 41, Folder 98)
  - 2885 (Box 41, Folder 99)
  - 2922 (Box 41, Folder 100)
  - 2942 (Box 41, Folder 101)
  - 3015 (Box 41, Folder 102)
  - 3016 (Box 41, Folder 103)
  - 3020 (Box 41, Folder 104)
  - 3047 (Box 41, Folder 105)
  - 3068 (Box 41, Folder 106)
  - 3176 (Box 41, Folder 107)
  - 3177 (Box 41, Folder 108)
  - 3178 (Box 41, Folder 109)
  - 3179 (Box 41, Folder 110)
  - 3189 (Box 41, Folder 111)
  - 3203 (Box 41, Folder 112)
  - 3213 (Box 41, Folder 113)
  - 3216 (Box 41, Folder 114)
  - 3223 (Box 41, Folder 115)
  - 3240 (Box 41, Folder 116)
  - 3261 (Box 41, Folder 117)
  - 3346 (Box 41, Folder 118)
  - 3357 (Box 41, Folder 119)
  - 3361 (Box 41, Folder 120)
  - 3416 (Box 41, Folder 121)
  - 3423 (Box 41, Folder 122)
  - 3449 (Box 41, Folder 123)
  - 3493 (Box 41, Folder 124)
  - 3494 (Box 41, Folder 125)
  - 3503 (Box 41, Folder 126)
  - 3511 (Box 41, Folder 127)
  - 3517 (Box 41, Folder 128)
  - 3518 (Box 41, Folder 129)
  - 3520 (Box 41, Folder 130)
  - 3542 (Box 41, Folder 131)
  - 3549 (Box 41, Folder 132)
  - 80 (Box 41, Folder 133)
  - 113, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 134)
  - 154 (Box 41, Folder 135)
  - 218 (Box 41, Folder 136)
  - 260 (Box 41, Folder 137)
  - 336 (Box 41, Folder 138)
  - 446 (Box 41, Folder 139)
  - 464 (Box 41, Folder 140)
  - 466 (Box 41, Folder 141)
  - 512 (Box 41, Folder 142)
  - 553 (Box 41, Folder 143)
  - 603 (Box 41, Folder 144)
  - 622 (Box 41, Folder 145)
  - 625 (Box 41, Folder 146)
  - 661 (Box 41, Folder 147)
  - 697 (Box 41, Folder 148)
  - 770 (Box 41, Folder 149)
  - 805 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 814 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 1010 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 1231 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 1274 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 1452 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 1503 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 1515 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 1539 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - 1543 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - 1586 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - 1605 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - 1647 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - 1665 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - 1670 (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
  - 1731 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - 1733 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - 1743 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - 1778 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - 1813 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - 1853 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - 1855 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - 1856 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - 1860 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - 1894 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - 1917 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - 1980 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - 2034 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - 2056 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - 2221 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - 2298 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - 2431 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - 2484 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - 2486 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - 2487 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - 2488 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - 2600 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - 2695 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - 2792 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - 3074 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - 3075 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - 3076 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - 3077 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - 3149 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - 3162 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - 3187 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - 3195 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - 3218 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - 3384 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - 3391 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - 3392 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - 3456 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - 3502 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - 3569 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - 3727 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - 3742 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - 3773 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - 3796 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - 3868 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - 3869 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - 3870 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - 3871 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - 3872 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - 3893 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - 3894 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - 3911 (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - 3919 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - 3924 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - 3943 (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - 3944 (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - 13 (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - 17, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - 18 (Box 42, Folder 74)
  - 61 (Box 42, Folder 75)
  - 73 (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - 176 (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - 232 (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - 282 (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - 375 (Box 42, Folder 80)
  - 376 (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - 386 (Box 42, Folder 82)
  - 408 (Box 42, Folder 83)
  - 450 (Box 42, Folder 84)
  - 457 (Box 42, Folder 85)
  - 509 (Box 42, Folder 86)
  - 529 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  - 534 (Box 42, Folder 88)
  - 598 (Box 42, Folder 90)
  - 635 (Box 42, Folder 91)
  - 722 (Box 42, Folder 92)
  - 773 (Box 42, Folder 93)
  - 847 (Box 42, Folder 94)
  - 894 (Box 42, Folder 95)
  - 903 (Box 42, Folder 96)